<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20190409</CreaDate><CreaTime>15533000</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>FALSE</SyncOnce><DataProperties><itemProps><itemName Sync="TRUE">ODFW_wildlife_mgmt_units</itemName><imsContentType Sync="TRUE">002</imsContentType><nativeExtBox><westBL Sync="TRUE">221928.523622</westBL><eastBL Sync="TRUE">2345049.675197</eastBL><southBL Sync="TRUE">88600.882546</southBL><northBL Sync="TRUE">1675008.103346</northBL><exTypeCode Sync="TRUE">1</exTypeCode></nativeExtBox><itemSize Sync="TRUE">8.203</itemSize><itemLocation><linkage Sync="TRUE">file://\\fwhqd\GIS\Game_program\Gis_data\Boundaries\Odfw\WMU_rev_2016\Revised_shapefile\ODFW_wildlife_mgmt_units.shp</linkage><protocol Sync="TRUE">Local Area Network</protocol></itemLocation></itemProps><coordRef><type Sync="TRUE">Projected</type><geogcsn Sync="TRUE">GCS_North_American_1983</geogcsn><csUnits Sync="TRUE">Linear Unit: Foot (0.304800)</csUnits><projcsn Sync="TRUE">NAD_1983_Oregon_Statewide_Lambert_Feet_Intl</projcsn><peXml Sync="TRUE">&lt;ProjectedCoordinateSystem xsi:type='typens:ProjectedCoordinateSystem' xmlns:xsi='http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance' xmlns:xs='http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema' xmlns:typens='http://www.esri.com/schemas/ArcGIS/10.6'&gt;&lt;WKT&gt;PROJCS[&amp;quot;NAD_1983_Oregon_Statewide_Lambert_Feet_Intl&amp;quot;,GEOGCS[&amp;quot;GCS_North_American_1983&amp;quot;,DATUM[&amp;quot;D_North_American_1983&amp;quot;,SPHEROID[&amp;quot;GRS_1980&amp;quot;,6378137.0,298.257222101]],PRIMEM[&amp;quot;Greenwich&amp;quot;,0.0],UNIT[&amp;quot;Degree&amp;quot;,0.0174532925199433]],PROJECTION[&amp;quot;Lambert_Conformal_Conic&amp;quot;],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;False_Easting&amp;quot;,1312335.958005249],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;False_Northing&amp;quot;,0.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Central_Meridian&amp;quot;,-120.5],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Standard_Parallel_1&amp;quot;,43.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Standard_Parallel_2&amp;quot;,45.5],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Latitude_Of_Origin&amp;quot;,41.75],UNIT[&amp;quot;Foot&amp;quot;,0.3048],AUTHORITY[&amp;quot;EPSG&amp;quot;,2992]]&lt;/WKT&gt;&lt;XOrigin&gt;-118489100&lt;/XOrigin&gt;&lt;YOrigin&gt;-97381100&lt;/YOrigin&gt;&lt;XYScale&gt;37592196.316242374&lt;/XYScale&gt;&lt;ZOrigin&gt;-100000&lt;/ZOrigin&gt;&lt;ZScale&gt;10000&lt;/ZScale&gt;&lt;MOrigin&gt;-100000&lt;/MOrigin&gt;&lt;MScale&gt;10000&lt;/MScale&gt;&lt;XYTolerance&gt;0.0032808398950131233&lt;/XYTolerance&gt;&lt;ZTolerance&gt;0.001&lt;/ZTolerance&gt;&lt;MTolerance&gt;0.001&lt;/MTolerance&gt;&lt;HighPrecision&gt;true&lt;/HighPrecision&gt;&lt;WKID&gt;2992&lt;/WKID&gt;&lt;LatestWKID&gt;2992&lt;/LatestWKID&gt;&lt;/ProjectedCoordinateSystem&gt;</peXml></coordRef></DataProperties><SyncDate>20190409</SyncDate><SyncTime>15565800</SyncTime><ModDate>20190409</ModDate><ModTime>15565800</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><dataIdInfo><envirDesc Sync="TRUE"> Version 6.2 (Build 9200) ; Esri ArcGIS 10.6.0.8321</envirDesc><dataLang><languageCode value="eng" Sync="TRUE"/><countryCode value="USA" Sync="TRUE"/></dataLang><idCitation><resTitle Sync="FALSE">ODFW Wildlife Management Units</resTitle><presForm><PresFormCd value="005" Sync="TRUE"/></presForm></idCitation><spatRpType><SpatRepTypCd value="001" Sync="TRUE"/></spatRpType><dataExt><geoEle xmlns=""><GeoBndBox esriExtentType="search"><exTypeCode Sync="TRUE">1</exTypeCode><westBL Sync="TRUE">-124.811540</westBL><eastBL Sync="TRUE">-116.416198</eastBL><northBL Sync="TRUE">46.344633</northBL><southBL Sync="TRUE">41.920020</southBL></GeoBndBox></geoEle></dataExt><idPurp>For the purpose of managing Oregon's wildlife, the State has been divided into separate described areas called wildlife units or wildlife management units (WMUs). The digital version of the WMUs was published in 2010 and revised in 2016. The 2016 version extended the northern boundary of several units along the lower Columbia River north to the state boundary rather than the southern shoreline of the Columbia River.
</idPurp><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;These areas are called wildlife units. Whenever reference is made to a wildlife unit by name or designated number in any rule of the department, the area description provided in Division 080 shall apply, unless otherwise specified by the given rule. Areas described within a Wildlife Unit as a subunit are also described by a number which includes the Wildlife Unit number as its last two digits. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 30;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 30;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 30;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 30;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;DIVISION 080 WILDLIFE UNITS&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;https://www.dfw.state.or.us/OARs/80.pdf&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;DIVISION 080 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;WILDLIFE UNITS &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0000 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Wildlife Units &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;For the purpose of managing Oregon's wildlife, the State has been divided into separate described areas. These areas are called wildlife units. Whenever reference is made to a wildlife unit by name or designated number in any rule of the department, the area description provided in Division 080 shall apply, unless otherwise specified by the given rule. Areas described within a Wildlife Unit as a subunit are also described by a number which includes the Wildlife Unit number as its last two digits. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0010 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Saddle Mountain Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Saddle Mountain Unit, number 10, is that area beginning at the mouth of Columbia River; east along state line to mouth of Clatskanie River; south along Clatskanie River to town of Clatskanie; south on State Highway 47 to Timber-Vernonia Highway; southwest on Timber-Vernonia Highway to U.S. Highway 26; northwest on U.S. Highway 26 to State Highway 53 at Necanicum Junction; southwest on State Highway 53 to North Fork Nehalem River; southwest along North Fork Nehalem River and north shoreline of Nehalem Bay to Pacific Ocean; north along Pacific Ocean coastline to state line at mouth of Columbia River, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 72-1989, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 8-15-89 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0011 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Scappoose Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Scappoose Unit, number 11, is that area beginning at Vernonia; northeast on State Highway 47 to Clatskanie; north along Clatskanie River to state line in Columbia River; southeast along state line to Willamette River; southwest along Willamette River to Multnomah Channel; northwest along Multnomah Channel to U.S. Highway 30 at Sauvie Island bridge; northwest on U.S. Highway 30 to Cornelius Pass Road; southwest on Cornelius Pass Road to U.S. Highway 26; northwest on U.S. Highway 26 to State Highway 6; west on State Highway 6 to Glenwood; northwest on Glenwood-Timber-Vernonia Highway to State Highway 47; north on State Highway 47 to Vernonia, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0012 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Wilson Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Wilson Unit, number 12, is that area beginning on the north shoreline at the mouth of Tillamook Bay; north along Pacific Ocean coastline to north shoreline of Nehalem Bay; northeast along north shoreline of Nehalem Bay and North Fork Nehalem River to State Highway 53 bridge; northeast on State Highway 53 to U.S. Highway 26 at Necanicum Junction; southeast on U.S. Highway 26 to Timber-Glenwood Highway; south on Timber-Glenwood Highway to Glenwood; southwest on State Highway 6 to Wilson River at Mills Bridge; west along Wilson River and north shoreline of Tillamook Bay to mouth, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 17-1996, f. 4-10-96, cert. ef. 4-15-96 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0014 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Trask Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Trask Unit, number 14, is that area beginning at McMinnville; southwest on State Highway 18 to Salmon River; west along Salmon River to Pacific Ocean; north along Pacific Ocean coastline to north shoreline at mouth of Tillamook Bay; east along north shoreline of Tillamook Bay and Wilson River to State Highway 6 at Mills Bridge; northeast on State Highway 6 to State Highway 8 near Gales Creek; southeast on State Highway 8 to State Highway 47 at Forest Grove; south on State Highway 47 to State Highway 99W; southwest on State Highway 99W to McMinnville, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 17-1996, f. 4-10-96, cert. ef. 4-15-96 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0015 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Willamette Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Willamette Unit, number 15, is that area beginning at Sandy; southwest on State Highway 211 to State Highway 213; southwest on State High way 213 to Cascade Highway at Silverton; south on the Cascade Highway to State Highway 22; east on State Highway 22 to Mehama; south to Lyons; south and west on State Highway 226 to Richardson Gap Road east of Scio; south on Richardson Gap Road to Baptist Church Drive; east on Baptist Church Drive to Kowitz Road; south on Kowitz Road to Lacomb Road; west on Lacomb Road to Brewster Roads; south on Brewster Road to State Highway 34; west on State Highway 34 to Interstate Highway 5; south on Interstate Highway 5 to Belt Line Road; west and south on Belt Line Road to State Highway 126; west on State Highway 126 to Poodle Creek Road; north on Poodle Creek Road to State Highway 36; northeast on State Highway 36 to Territorial Road near Cheshire; north on Territorial Road to Monroe; north on State Highway 99W to Dawson Road (County Road 45200); west on Dawson Road to Bellfountain; north on Bellfountain Road to Decker Road at In vale School; west on Decker Road to State Highway 34; northeast on State Highway 34 to Corvallis; north on State Highway 99W to Airlie Road (No. 7) at Suver; northwesterly on Airlie Road to State Highway 223; north on State Highway 223 to Perrydale Road at Dallas; north on Perrydale Road to State Highway 22; northwest on State Highway 22 to State Highway 18; northeast on State Highway 18 to State Highway 99W; north on State Highway 99W to State Highway 47; north on State Highway 47 to State Highway 8; northwest on State Highway 8 to State Highway 6; east on State Highway 6 to U.S. Highway 26; southeast on U.S. Highway 26 to Cornelius Pass Road; northeast on Cornelius Pass Road to U.S. Highway 30; southeast on U.S. Highway 30 to Multnomah Channel at the Sauvie Island bridge; southeast along Multnomah Channel to Willamette River; northeast down Willamette River to state line in the Columbia River; southeast along state line to Sandy River; southeast up Sandy River to Teneyck Road; south on Teneyck Road to Sandy, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: Adopted 10-7-05, ef. 1-1-06 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0016 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Santiam Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Santiam Unit, number 16, is that area beginning at Lebanon; north on Brewster Road to Lacomb Road; east on Lacomb Road to Kowitz Road; north on Kowitz Road to Baptist Church Drive; west on Baptist Church Drive to Richardson Gap Road; north on Richardson Gap Road to State Highway 226; northeast on State Highway 226; west on State Highway 22 to Cascade Highway near Stayton; north on Cascade Highway to State Highway 213 at Silverton; northeast on State Highway 213 to State Highway 211; northeast on State Highway 211 to Sandy; north on Teneyck Road to Sandy River; northwest down Sandy River to state line in Columbia River; northeast along state line to Multnomah-Hood River County line; southeast along Multnomah-Hood River County line to Lolo Pass; southeast along Pacific Crest Trail to Barlow Pass; west on Highway 35 to Highway 26; southeast on Highway 26 to junction of Highway 216; west and then south along the west boundary of The Confederated Tribes of Warm Springs Indian Reservation of Oregon (CTWSRO) (McQuinn Strip line) to summit of Mt. Jefferson; south along the west CTWSRO boundary and the Cascade crest (Jefferson/Linn Co. line) to the junction of the Pacific Crest National Scenic Trail (PCT) in Township 11 South Range 8 East Sec 17 then south on PCT to U.S. Highway 20/126 at Santiam Pass. ; PCT west on U.S. Highway 20 to Lebanon; point of beginning. (The McQuinn Strip portion of the White River Unit and the Warm Springs Indian Reservation was closed to public hunting September 21, 1992 until further notice). &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0017 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stott Mountain Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Stott Mountain Unit, number 17, is that area beginning at Dallas; south on State Highway 223 to Gardner Road (No. 865); northwest on Gardner Road and Bridgeport Road (No. 864) to Falls City; west on Valsetz Road to South Fork of Siletz River; downstream along South Fork of Siletz River, main Siletz River and north shoreline of Siletz Bay to Pacific Ocean; north along Pacific Ocean coastline to mouth of Salmon River; east along Salmon River to State Highway 18 near Rose Lodge; east on State Highway 18 to State Highway 22 near Valley Junction; southeast on State Highway 22 to Perrydale Road; south on Perrydale Road to State Highway 223 at Dallas, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0018 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Alsea Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Alsea Unit, number 18, is that area beginning at Corvallis; southwest on State Highway 34 to Decker Road; southeast on Decker Road to Bell fountain Road; south on Bellfountain Road to Bellfountain; east on Dawson Road (County Road 45200) to State Highway 99W; south on State Highway 99W to Monroe; south on Territorial Road to State Highway 36; southwest on State Highway 36 to north shoreline of Triangle Lake; southwest along Triangle Lake shoreline, Lake Creek, Siuslaw River and north shoreline of Siuslaw Bay to Pacific Ocean; north along Pacific Ocean coastline to north shoreline of Siletz Bay; easterly along north shoreline of Siletz Bay, Siletz River and South Fork of Siletz River to Valsetz; east on Valsetz-Falls City main county road to Falls City; southeast along Bridgeport Road (No. 864), Gardner Road (No. 865) and Airlie Road (No. 7) to State Highway 99W; south on State Highway 99W to Corvallis, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0019 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;McKenzie Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The McKenzie Unit, number 19, is that area beginning at Lebanon; east on U.S. Highway 20 to Pacific Crest Trail; south along Pacific Crest Trail to State Highway 58; northwest on State Highway 58 to Inter state Highway 5; north on Interstate Highway 5 to State Highway 34; east on State Highway 34 to Lebanon, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 6-1995, f. 1-23-95, cert. ef. 4-1-95 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0020 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Siuslaw Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Siuslaw Unit, number 20, is that area beginning at Interstate 5-Belt Line Road junction north of Eugene; south on Interstate 5 to Drain junction and State Highway 99; southwest on State Highway 99 to Drain; west on State Highway 38 to Umpqua River at Elkton; west along Umpqua River and south shoreline of Winchester Bay to Pacific Ocean; north along Pacific Ocean coastline to north shoreline of Siuslaw Bay; northeast along north shoreline of Siuslaw Bay, Siuslaw River, Lake Creek and north shoreline of Triangle Lake to State Highway 36; south on State Highway 36 to Poodle Creek junction; south on Poodle Creek Road to State Highway 126; east on State Highway 126 to Belt Line Road; northeast on Belt Line Road to Interstate 5, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0021 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Indigo Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Indigo Unit, number 21, is that area beginning at Oakridge; southeast on State Highway 58 to Pacific Crest Trail; south along Pacific Crest Trail to State Highway 138; north and west on State Highway 138 to Toketee junction; north on Toketee Road to North Umpqua River; west along North Umpqua River to Dixonville-Albany main power transmission line; north on Dixonville-Albany main power transmission line to Shoestring Road; east on Shoestring Road .8-mile to London Road; north on London Road and South 6th Street to Interstate Highway 5; north on Interstate Highway 5 to State Highway 58; southeast on State Highway 58 to Oakridge, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0022 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Dixon Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Dixon Unit, number 22, is that area beginning at Shady Cove; northwest on State Highway 227 to Dixonville-Hanna Nickel main power transmission line at a point approximately two miles west of Days Creek; north along main power transmission line to North Umpqua River; east along North Umpqua River to Toketee; south on Toketee Road to State Highway 138; east and south on State Highway 138 to State Highway 230; southwest on State Highway 230 to State Highway 62; southwest on State Highway 62 to Shady Cove, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0023 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Melrose Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Melrose Unit, number 23, is that area beginning at Dixonville power substation; south along Dixonville-Nickel Mountain main power transmission line to Douglas County Rd 1 at a point approximately two miles west of Days Creek; southwest on Douglas County Rd 1 to Canyonville; south on Interstate Highway 5, 3/4-mile to Dixonville-Nickel Mountain main power transmission line; west on Dixonville-Nickel Mountain main power transmission line to Southern Pacific railroad tracks adjacent to the Nickel Mountain Road junction; southwest along SPRR tracks to the Union Creek Road; north on Union Creek Road to Live Oak Cr. Rd.; northeast on Live Oak Cr. Rd. through Horse Prairie and Olalla Creek Road to Ireland Rd.; west on Ireland Rd. to Benedict Rd.; north on Benedict Rd. to Tenmile; north on Reston and Flournoy Valley roads to Melrose; north on Melrose-Umpqua Road to the Umpqua River and Umpqua; north along the Umpqua River to State Highway 38 at Elkton; east on State Highway 38 to Drain; northeast on State Highway 99 to Curtin; northeast on Interstate 5 to South 6th Street, south on South 6th Street to London Road; south on London Road to Shoestring Road; west .8-mile on Shoestring Road to the Albany-Dixonville main power transmission line; south along Albany-Dixonville main power transmission line to Dixonville, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0024 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Tioga Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Tioga Unit, number 24, is that area beginning at Coquille; north on State Highway 42 and U.S. Highway l0l to south shoreline of Coos Bay; southwest along south shoreline of Coos Bay to Pacific Ocean; north along Pacific Ocean coastline to south shoreline of Winchester Bay; easterly along south shoreline of Winchester Bay and Umpqua River to Umpqua; south on Umpqua-Melrose Road to Melrose; south on Flournoy Valley and Reston roads to Tenmile; west on State Highway 42 to Coquille, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0025 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Sixes Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Sixes Unit, number 25, is that area beginning at Gold Beach; north along Pacific Ocean coastline to south shoreline of Coos Bay; easterly along south shore of Coos Bay to U.S. Highway 101; south on U.S. Highway 101 to State Highway 42; southeast on State Highway 42 to Powers Highway; southeast on Powers Highway to Powers; south on posted forest road to Rogue River at Illahee; southwest along Rogue River to Gold Beach, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 72-1989, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 8-15-89 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0026 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Powers Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Powers Unit, number 26, is that area beginning at Grave Creek Bridge on Rogue River; west on Rogue River to Illahee; north on posted forest road to Powers; northwest on Powers Highway to State Highway 42; east on State Highway 42 to Tenmile; south on Benedict Rd. to Ireland Rd.; east on Ireland Rd. to Olalla Cr. Rd.; south on Olalla Creek Road through Horse Prairie to Live Oak Cr. Rd.; southwest on Live Oak Cr. Rd. to Union Creek Road; northeast on SPRR tracks to Dixonville-Nickle Mountain main power transmission line adjacent to Nickel Mountain Road; east along main power transmission line to Interstate Highway 5; south on Interstate Highway 5 to Wolf Creek; southwest on Wolf Creek-Grave Creek Road to Grave Creek Bridge, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0027 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Chetco Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Chetco Unit, number 27, is that area beginning at Gold Beach; east along Rogue River to Grants Pass; southwest on U.S. Highway 199 to Oregon-California state line; west along state line to Pacific Ocean; northwest along Pacific Ocean coastline to Gold Beach, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 72-1989, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 8-15-89 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0028 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Applegate Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Applegate Unit, number 28, is that area beginning at Grants Pass; east and southeast on Interstate Highway 5 to Oregon-California state line; west along state line to U.S. Highway 199; northeast on U.S. Highway 199 to Grants Pass, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 72-1989, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 8-15-89 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0029 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Evans Creek Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Evans Creek Unit, number 29, is that area beginning at Grants Pass; northwest along the Rogue River to Grave Creek Bridge; northeast on Grave Creek-Wolf Creek Road to Interstate Highway 5 at Wolf Creek; north on Interstate Highway 5 to Canyonville; east and south on State Highway 227 to Shady Cove; south on State Highway 62 to Medford; northwest on Interstate Highway 5 to Grants Pass, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0030 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Rogue Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Rogue Unit, number 30, is that area beginning at Medford; north on State Highway 62 to State Highway 230; northeast on State Highway 230 to Diamond Lake State Highway 138; south and east on State Highway 138 to Pacific Crest Trail; south along Pacific Crest Trail to boundary of Crater Lake National Park; west, south and east along Crater Lake National Park boundary to Pacific Crest Trail; south along Pacific Crest Trail; southeast on Forest Trail 993 along Fourmile Lake; south on Forest Road 3661 to State Highway 140; west on State Highway 140 to Forest Road 3601; south Forest Road 3601 to Dead Indian Road; southwest on Dead Indian Road to Jackson-Klamath county line; south along Jackson-Klamath county line to State Highway 66; west on State Highway 66 to Copco Road; south on Copco Road to Oregon-California state line; west along Oregon-California state line to Interstate Highway 5; north on Interstate Highway 5 to Medford, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: Adopted 10-11-03, ef. 1-1-04 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0031 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Keno Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Keno Unit, number 31, is that area beginning at Klamath Falls; south on U.S. Highway 97 to Oregon-California state line; west along Oregon-California state line to Copco Road; north on Copco Road to State Highway 66; east on State Highway 66 to Jackson-Klamath county line; north on Jackson-Klamath county line to Dead Indian Road; northeast on Dead Indian Road to Forest Road 3601; north on Forest Road 3601 to State Highway 140; east on State Highway 140 to Forest Road 3661; north on Forest Road 366l to Fourmile Lake; northwest on Forest Trail 993 to Pacific Crest Trail; north on Pacific Crest Trail to south boundary of Crater Lake National Park; east along south boundary of Crater Lake National Park to State Highway 62; southeast on State Highway 62 to U.S. Highway 97; south on U.S. Highway 97 to Klamath Falls, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: Adopted 10-11-03, ef. 1-1-04 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0032 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Klamath Falls Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Klamath Falls Unit, number 32, is that area beginning at Klamath Falls; north on U.S. Highway 97 to Williamson River; north along Williamson River to confluence of Sprague River; east along Sprague River to Godowa Springs Road north of Beatty; south on Godowa Springs Road to State Highway 140 at Beatty; east on State Highway 140 to Bly; southwest on Gerber Road past Gerber Reservoir to East Langell Valley Road; south on East Langell Valley Road to Lost River; southeast along Lost River to Oregon-California state line; west along state line to U.S. Highway 97; northeast on U.S. Highway 97 to Klamath Falls, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0033 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Sprague Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Sprague Unit, number 33, is that area beginning at Chiloquin; south along Williamson River to U.S. Highway 97; north on U.S. Highway 97 to State Highway 62; northwest on State Highway 62 to Crater Lake National Park boundary; east and north along Crater Lake National Park boundary to Sand Creek; east along Sand Creek to Scott Creek Road 66; east on Scott Creek Road one mile to U.S. Highway 97; east on Silver Lake Road to Williamson River; upstream north, east and south along Williamson River to Yamsey Guard Station; southeast on Forest Road 44 to Sycan River at Powers Crossing; south along Sycan River to Sprague River; west along Sprague River to Williamson River at Chiloquin, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0034 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Upper Deschutes Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Upper Deschutes Unit, number 34, is that area beginning at Bend; southwest on U.S. Highway 97 to Crescent; west on Klamath County Road 61to Crescent Creek; southwest on Crescent Creek to State Highway 58; northwest on State Highway 58 to Pacific Crest Trail; north along Pacific Crest Trail to U.S. Highway 242; east on State Highway 242 to Sisters; east on State Highway 126 to Redmond; southwest on U.S. Highway 97 to Bend, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 1-01-08 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0035 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Paulina Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Paulina Unit, number 35, is that area beginning at Redmond; east on State Highway 126 to Prineville; southeast on State Highway 27 to U.S. Highway 20; northwest on U.S. Highway 20 to Millican-Lake Road 2-1/2 miles east of Millican; southeast and south on Millican-Lake Road past Dickerson and Janes Well (Lake County Road 5-12D) to intersection of Lake County Road 5-12B; east on Lake County Road 5-12B to intersection of Lake County Road 5-14C to junction of Lake County Road 5-14D; continue southwest and south on Lake County Road 5-14C to junction of Lake County Road 5-14, 2 miles east of Christmas Valley; west on Wagontire Road (Lake County Road 5-14) to Christmas Valley; west and north on Fort Rock Road (Lake County Road 5-10) to State Highway; northwest on State Highway 31 to Gilchrist main logging road 9775 between mileposts 16 and 17; west on Gilchrist main logging road to U.S. Highway 97; northeast on U.S. Highway 97 to Redmond, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 30-2000, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-14-00 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0036 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Maury Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Maury Unit, number 36, is that area beginning at Brothers on U.S. Highway 20; northwest on U.S. Highway 20 to State Highway 27; north on State Highway 27 to Prineville Dam; east along Prineville Reservoir, Crooked River and Beaver Creek to Paulina; easterly on main county road to Grindstone Creek Road; southeast on Grindstone Creek Road to Twelvemile Creek Road; west on Twelvemile Creek Road to Camp Creek-Glass Buttes Road; south on Camp Creek-Glass Buttes Road to U.S. Highway 20 near Glass Buttes; northwest on U.S. Highway 20 to Brothers, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0037 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Ochoco Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Ochoco Unit, number 37, is that area beginning at Prineville; northeast on U.S. Highway 26 to Dayville; south along South Fork John Day River to Pine Creek Road; west on Pine Creek Road to Suplee; west on county road to Paulina; west along Beaver Creek, Crooked River and Prineville Reservoir to State Highway 27 at Prineville Dam; northwest on State Highway 27 to Prineville, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0038 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Grizzly Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Grizzly Unit, number 38, is that area beginning at Redmond; north on U.S. Highway 97 to Crooked River; north along Crooked River and Deschutes River to South Junction; northeast on South Junction county road to junction with U.S. Highway 97 and U.S. Highway 197; south on U.S. Highway 97 to Antelope Creek Road; northeast on Antelope Creek Road to Antelope; east on State Highway 218 to John Day River at Clarno; southeast along John Day River to Bridge Creek; southeast along Bridge Creek to U.S. Highway 26 near Mitchell; southwest on U.S. Highway 26 to Prineville; west on U.S. Highway 126 to Redmond, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0039 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Metolius Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Metolius Unit, number 39, is that area beginning at Sisters; west on State Highway 242 to Pacific Crest Trail; north along Pacific Crest Trail to south boundary of Warm Springs Indian Reservation; east along Warm Springs Indian Reservation boundary following Jefferson Creek and Metolius River to Lake Billy Chinook; south along Lake Billy Chinook to Crooked River; southeast along Crooked River to U.S. Highway 97; south on U.S. Highway 97 to Redmond; west on State Highway 126 to Sisters, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 6-1995, f. 1-23-95, cert. ef. 4-1-95 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0040 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Maupin Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Maupin Unit, number 40, is that area beginning at Maupin; north on U.S. Highway 197 to Tygh Valley; northeast on State Highway 216 to Grass Valley; south on U.S. Highway 97 to Shaniko; southeast on State Highway 218 to Antelope; southwest on Antelope Creek Road to U.S. Highway 97; north on U.S. Highway 97 to junction of U.S. Highway 197 and South Junction Road; southwest on South Junction Road to Deschutes River at South Junction; northeast along Deschutes River to Maupin, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0041 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;White River Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The White River Unit, number 41, is that area beginning at The Dalles; east along Columbia River to U.S. Highway 197; south on U.S. Highway 197 to Deschutes River at Maupin; south along Deschutes River to north boundary of Warm Springs Indian Reservation boundary; west along northern Warm Springs Indian Reservation boundary (McQuinn Strip line) to the junction of Highway 216 and Highway 26; northwest on Highway 26 to junction of Highway 35; northeast on Highway 35 to Hood River; east along the Columbia River to The Dalles; point of beginning. (The McQuinn Strip portion of the White River Unit and the Warm Springs Indian Reservation was closed to public hunting September 21, 1992 until further notice). &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146, &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146, &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 6-1995, f. 1-23-95, cert. ef. 4-1-95 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0042 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hood Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Hood Unit, number 42, is that area beginning at Hood River; southwest on State Highway 35 to Barlow Pass (Pacific Crest Trail); northwest along Pacific Crest Trail to Lolo Pass; northwest along Hood River-Multnomah county line to Columbia River near Bonneville; east along Columbia River to Hood River, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0043 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Biggs Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Biggs Unit, number 43, is that area beginning at Arlington; south on State Highway 19 to Fossil; southwest on State Highway 218 to Shaniko; north on U.S. Highway 97 to Grass Valley; southwest on State Highway 216 to Tygh Valley; north on U.S. Highway 197 to the Columbia River; east along the Columbia River to Arlington, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 72-1989, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 8-15-89 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0044 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Columbia Basin Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Columbia Basin Unit, number 44, is that area beginning at Condon; north on State Highway 19 to Oregon-Washington state line at Arlington; northeast along state line to State Highway 11; southwest on State Highway 11 to Pendleton; southwest on U.S. Highway 395 to State Highway 74; southwest on State Highway 74 to Heppner; southwest on State Highway 207 to State Highway 206; west on State Highway 206 to Condon, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 72-1989, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 8-15-89 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0045 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Fossil Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Fossil Unit, number 45, is that area beginning at Fossil; north on State Highway 19 to Condon; east on State Highway 206 to State Highway 207; south on State Highway 207 to State Highway 19; southeast on State Highway 19 to U.S. Highway 26; west on U.S. Highway 26 to Bridge Creek near Mitchell; northwest along Bridge Creek to John Day River; northwest along John Day River to State Highway 218 at Clarno; northeast on State Highway 218 to Fossil, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 72-1989, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 8-15-89 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0046 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Murderers Creek Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Murderers Creek Unit, number 46, is that area beginning at Dayville; east on U.S. Highway 26 to Prairie City; southeast on County Road 62 to Summit Prairie; west on Logan Valley County Road 16 to Seneca; south on U.S. Highway 395 to Forest Road 37; southwest on Forest Road 37 to Forest Road 3750; west on Forest Road 3750 to South Fork John Day River; northwest along South Fork John Day River to Dayville, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0047 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Northside Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Northside Unit, number 47, is that area beginning at John Day; northwest on U.S. Highway 26 to State Highway 19; north on State Highway 19 to North Fork John Day River at Kimberly; northeast along North Fork John Day River to Long Creek Road at Monument; southeast on Long Creek Road to Long Creek; north on U.S. Highway 395 to Middle Fork John Day River Road; southeast on Middle Fork John Day River Road to State Highway 7; south on State Highway 7 to U.S. Highway 26; southwest on U.S. Highway 26 to John Day, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0048 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Heppner Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Heppner Unit, number 48, is that area beginning at Heppner; northeast on State Highway 74 to U.S. Highway 395; south on U.S. Highway 395 to Long Creek-Monument Road; northwest on Long Creek-Monument Road to North Fork John Day River at Monument; southwest along North Fork John Day River to State Highway 19 at Kimberly; northwest on State Highway 19 to State Highway 207; north on State Highway 207 to Heppner, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0049 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Ukiah Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Ukiah Unit, number 49, is that area beginning at Pendleton; southeast on Interstate Highway 84 to Mt. Emily exit; west on county road to Kamela; southwest on Forest Road 2135400 to Forest Road 2135; southwest on Forest Road 2135 to Forest Road 21; southwest on Forest Road 21 to 2100040, south on 2100040 to Forest Road 5900230; south on 5900230 to State Highway 244 (Forest Road 59) at Four Corners Forest Camp; west on State Highway 244 (Forest Road 59) approximately two miles to Tower Mountain Road 5226; south and east on Tower Mountain Road 5226 past Frazier Forest Camp and Tower Mountain to Silver Butte Road 5225; south on Silver Butte Road 5225 to Meadow Creek; southwest along Meadow Creek to Big Creek; southwest along Big Creek to North Fork John Day River; northwest along North Fork John Day River to U.S. Highway 395 near Dale; north on U.S. Highway 395 to Pendleton, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0050 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Desolation Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Desolation Unit, number 50, is that area beginning at Dale on U.S. Highway 395; southeast along North Fork John Day River to Big Creek; northeast along Big Creek to Meadow Creek; northeast along Meadow Creek to Forest Road 5225 at Forks Guard Station; northwest on Forest Road 5225 to Granite-Ukiah Road 52; southeast on Granite-Ukiah Road 52 to Anthony Lakes Road 73; northeast on Anthony Lakes Road 73 to summit of Blue Mountains west of Anthony Lakes; south along summit of Blue Mts. to the summit of Anthony Lakes Ski Area (junction of Grant, Baker, and Union counties) southwest along Blue Mountain summit (Baker/ Grant county line) to State Highway 7; southwest on State Highway 7 to Co Rd 20; northwest on Co Rd 20 to U.S. Highway 395; north on U.S. Highway 395 to Dale, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 0-01.09 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0051 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Sumpter Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Sumpter Unit, number 51, is that area beginning at Ironside; northwest on U.S. Highway 26 to Austin junction; northeast on State Highway 7 to summit of Blue Mountains (Tipton Summit); northeast along Blue Mountain summit (Baker/ Grant County line) to the Summit of Anthony Lakes Ski Area (junction of Grant, Baker, and Union counties); north along the Blue Mt summit to Anthony Lakes Road 73 ; northeast on Anthony Lakes Road to Ellis Rd; north on Ellis Rd to North Powder River Ln; east on North Powder River Ln to Interstate Highway 84 at North Powder; southeast on Interstate Highway 84 to Durbin Creek Road overpass; west on Durbin Creek-Malheur Reservoir Road to Ironside, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 1.01.09 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0052 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Starkey Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Starkey Unit, number 52, is that area beginning on Interstate Highway 84 at the junction of State Highway 82 at La Grande; southeast on Interstate Highway 84 to North Powder; west on North Powder River Lane and southwest on Anthony Lakes Road 73 to Anthony Lakes; west past Anthony Lakes to Granite-Ukiah Road 52; northwest on Granite-Ukiah Road 52 to Tower Mountain Road 5226; east and north on Tower Mountain Road 5226 past Tower Mountain and Frazier Forest Camp to State Highway 244 (Forest Road 59); east on State Highway 244 (Forest Road 59) to Forest Road 5900230 at Four Corners Forest Camp; north on road 5900230 to 2100040, north on 2100040 to Forest Road 21; north on Forest Road 21 to Forest Road 2135; northeast on Forest Road 2135 to Forest Road 2135400; northeast on Forest Road 2135400 to Kamela; east on Summit Road to Interstate Highway 84; southeast on Interstate Highway 84 to State Highway 82 at La Grande, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 30-2000, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-14-00 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0053 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Catherine Creek Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Catherine Creek Unit, number 53, is that area beginning at Elgin; northeast on State Highway 82 to Minam; south along Minam River to the boundary of Wallowa-Whitman National Forest; west along forest boundary to Point Prominence Road (62 and 6220); south along Point Prominence Road to Moss Springs Campground; south and east from Moss Springs Campground on Lodgepole Trail 1920 to Cartwheel Ridge Trail 1907; north and east on Cartwheel Ridge Trail 1907 to the divide between the Catherine Creek and Minam River drainages past Burger Butte to Granite Butte; generally south on the divide between Catherine Creek and Eagle Creek drainages to Flagstaff Butte; west on Forest Road 7700582 to Forest Road 77; west on Forest Road 77 to Forest Road 6730; south on 6730 to Forest Road 6730310; west on 6730310 to Forest Road 6750300; west on 6750300 to Lick Creek Road 6750; south on Lick Creek Road 6750 to Big Creek Road 67; west on Big Creek Road to Medical Springs; southwest on State Highway 203 to the Powder River; northwest on Powder River to Interstate Highway 84 at North Powder; north on Interstate Highway 84 to State Highway 82 at La Grande; northeast on State Highway 82 to Elgin, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0054 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Mt. Emily Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Mt. Emily Unit, number 54, is that area beginning at Pendleton; northeast on State Highway 11 to Weston; southeast on State Highway 204 to Elgin; southwest on State Highway 82 to Interstate Highway 84 at La Grande; northwest on Interstate Highway 84 to Pendleton, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 30-2000, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-14-00 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0055 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Walla Walla Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Walla Walla Unit, number 55, is that area beginning at Weston; north on State Highway 11 to Oregon-Washington state line; east along state line to Forest Road 64; southwest on Forest Road 64 to Tollgate; northwest on State Highway 204 to Weston, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0056 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Wenaha Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Wenaha Unit, number 56, is that area beginning at Troy; southwest along Grande Ronde River to Elgin; northwest on State Highway 204 to Tollgate; northeast on Forest Road 64 to Oregon-Washington state line; east along state line to Grande Ronde River; southwest along Grande Ronde River to Troy, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0057 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Sled Springs Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Sled Springs Unit, number 57, is that area beginning at Wallowa; west on State Highway 82 to Elgin; northeast along Grande Ronde River to Oregon-Washington state line; east along state line to Joseph Creek; southwest along Joseph Creek to Chesnimnus Creek; southeast along Chesnimnus Creek to Crow Creek Road; south on Crow Creek Road to State Highway 82; northwest on State Highway 82 to Wallowa, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0058 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Chesnimnus Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Chesnimnus Unit, number 58, is that area beginning at Joseph; north on State Highway 82 to Crow Creek Road; north on Crow Creek Road to Chesnimnus Creek; northwest along Chesnimnus Creek to Joseph Creek; northeast along Joseph Creek to Oregon-Washington state line; east and southeast along state line to the Snake River; southeast along the Snake River to mouth of Imnaha River; southwest along Imnaha River to Imnaha; southwest on Sheep Creek Road to Joseph, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0059 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Snake River Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Snake River Unit, number 59, is that area beginning at confluence of Imnaha and Snake rivers; southeast along Snake River to Thirty-two Point Creek; southwest along Thirty-two Point Creek to Summit Road; southwest and northwest on Summit Road to North Fork Dry Creek; southwest along North Fork Dry Creek and northwest along Dry Creek to Imnaha River; north along Imnaha River to Snake River, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0060 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Minam Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Minam Unit, number 60, is that area beginning at the town of Minam; southeast on State Highway 82 to head of Wallowa Lake; southwest on West Fork Trail to Hawkins Pass; southwest along summit of Eagle Mountains to Granite Butte; northwest along summit separating Big Minam and Catherine Creek drainages past Burger Butte and Meadow Mountain to Cartwheel Ridge Trail 1907; West on Cartwheel Ridge Trail to Lodgepole Trail to Moss Springs; north on Point Prominence Road to the boundary of Wallowa-Whitman National Forest; north and east along National Forest boundary to Minam River; north along Minam River to State Highway 82 at the town of Minam, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 1-01-08 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0061 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Imnaha Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Imnaha Unit, number 61, is that area beginning at Joseph; northeast on Imnaha Highway to Imnaha; south and west along Imnaha River and South Fork of Imnaha River to Hawkins Pass; north on West Fork Trail to Wallowa Lake; north on State Highway 82 to Joseph, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 72-1989, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 8-15-89 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0062 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Pine Creek Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Pine Creek Unit, number 62, is that area beginning at Cornucopia; north on Blue Creek Trail (1865) to the summit of Eagle Mountains; west and south along summit of Eagle Mountains to Red Mt; west and south on summit of Eagle Mts to Crater Lake; north and west on summit if Eagle Mts to Krag Peak; north on summit of Eagle Mts to Jackson Peak; north to Hawkins Pass; east and north along South Fork Imnaha River and Imnaha River to Dry Creek; southeast along Dry Creek and northeast along North Fork Dry Creek to Summit Road; north and northeast on Summit Road to Thirty-two Point Creek; east along Thirty-two Point Creek to Snake River; south along Snake River to the mouth of Powder River; west along Powder River arm of Brownlee Reservoir to the old Richland-Halfway Highway (Sag Road); north on Sag Road to Highway 86; northeast on Highway 86 to Pine Creek; northwest along Pine Creek to Cornucopia, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 1.01.09 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0063 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Keating Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Keating Unit, number 63, is that area beginning at North Powder; northeast and southeast along Powder River to State Highway 203; northeast on State Highway 203 to Medical Springs; southeast and northeast on Big Creek Road 67 to Lick Creek; north on Lick Creek Road 6750 to Forest Road 6750300; east on Forest Road 6750300 to Forest Road 6730310; east on 6730310 to Forest Road 6730; north on 6730 to Forest Road 77; east on Forest Road 77 to Flagstaff Butte Road 7700582; east on road 7700582 to Flagstaff Butte; north along the divide between the Catherine Creek and Eagle Creek drainages to Granite Butte; east along summit of Eagle Mountains to Hawkins pass; south to Jackson Peak: south to Krag Peal; south and east to Crater Lake; north and east to Red Mt; north and east to Blue Creek Trail (1865) north of Cornucopia; south along Blue Creek Trail to Pine Creek; south and east along Pine Creek to State Highway 86; southwest on State Highway 86 to Old Richland-Halfway Highway (Sag Road); south on Sag Road to Powder River arm of Brownlee Reservoir; west along Powder River to State Highway 86 near Goose Cr; west on Highway 86 to Interstate Highway 84; north on Interstate Highway 84 to North Powder, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 1.01.09 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0064 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Lookout Mountain Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Lookout Mountain Unit, number 64, is that area beginning at junction of Interstate Highway 84 and State Highway 86 northeast of Baker; east on State Highway 86 to Powder River near Goose Creek; east along Powder River to Snake River; southwest along Snake River to mouth of Birch Creek at Farewell Bend; west along Birch Creek to Interstate Highway 84; northwest on Interstate Highway 84 to State Highway 86, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: FWC 72-1989, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 8-15-89 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0065 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Beulah Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Beulah Unit, number 65, is that area beginning at Vale; southwest on U.S. Highway 20 to Drewsey-Prairie City Road near Drewsey; northwest on Drewsey-Prairie City Road and Forest Road 1663 to the junction with Forest Road 14 near Antelope Mt.; northwest on Forest Road 14 and Forest Raod 16 to Summit Prairie; north on County Road 62 to U.S. Highway 26 near Prairie City; easterly on U.S. Highway 26 to Ironside; easterly on Malheur Reservoir Road to Interstate Highway 84; southeasterly on Interstate 84 to Birch Creek near Farewell Bend; easterly on Birch Creek to Snake River; southeast along Snake River to Nyssa; north and west on U.S. Highway 20 to Vale, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: Adopted 10-15-04, ef. 1-1-05 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0066 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Malheur River Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Malheur River Unit, number 66, is that area beginning at Burns; north on U.S. Highway 395 to Seneca; easterly on Logan Valley County Road #16 through Logan Valley to Forest Road 14; southeast on Forest Road 14 to the junction of Forest Road 1663 near Antelope Mt.; south of Forest Road 1663 and Otis Valley Road (Harney County Road 304) to Drewsey; south on Drewsey Rd (Harney County Road 305) to U.S. Highway 20; east on U.S. Highway 20 to Harper; southwest on Harper-Follyfarm Road to Follyfarm (Malheur County Roads 584 and 513) to State Highway 78 near Follyfarm; northwest on State Highway 78 to Burns, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: Adopted 10-7-05, ef. 1-1-06 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0067 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Owyhee Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Owyhee Unit, number 67, is that area beginning at Nyssa; south along Oregon-Idaho state line to Jordan Valley-Silver City Road; west on Jordan Valley-Silver City Road to Jordan Valley; southwest on U.S. Highway 95 to State Highway 78; northwest on State Highway 78 to Follyfarm; northeast on Follyfarm-Harper Road to Harper; east on U.S. Highway 20 to Nyssa, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0068 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Whitehorse Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Whitehorse Unit, number 68, is that area beginning at Follyfarm; southeast on State Highway 78 to U.S. Highway 95; northeast on U.S. Highway 95 to Jordan Valley; east on Jordan Valley-Silver City Road to Oregon-Idaho state line; south and west along state line to Denio; northeast on county road 201 through Fields and Andrews to Follyfarm, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: Adopted 10-7-05, ef. 1-1-06 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0069 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Steens Mountain Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Steens Mountain Unit, number 69, is that area beginning at the junction of State Highway 78 and State Highway 205, two miles east of Burns; southeast on State Highway 78 to East Steen Road (Harney County Road 201) near Follyfarm; southwest on East Steens Road through Andrews to Catlow Valley Road (Harney County Road 202) junction one mile north of Fields; northwest on Catlow Valley Road to Highway 205 at Frenchglen; north on State Highway 205 to Highway 78, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: Adopted 10-7-05, ef. 1-1-06 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0070 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Beatys Butte Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Beatys Butte Unit, number 70, is that area beginning at Denio; west along Oregon state line to Fort Bidwell-Warner Valley Road (Lake County Rd 3-14); north on 3-14 to Adel; north on county road 3-10 through Plush to county road 3-11; east on county road 3-11 to Hart Refuge and county road 3-12; north and east on 3-12 to Hart Refuge headquarters; east on Hart Mountain-Frenchglen road (Lake County Road 3-12) and Harney County Road 412 to Catlow Valley Road (Harney County Road 202); south and east on Catlow Valley Road to Harney County Rad 201, 1 mile north of Fields; south on County Road 201 through Fields to Denio, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: Adopted 10-7-05, ef. 1-1-06 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0071 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Juniper Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Juniper Unit, number 71, is that area beginning at Burns; east two miles on State Highway 78 to State Highway 205; south on State Highway 205 through Frenchglen to Hart Mountain Road (Harney County Road 412 and Lake County Road 3-12); west on Hart Mountain Road to Flagstaff Lake Road (Lake County Road 3-11); west on Flagstaff Lake Road to Hogback Road (Lake Country Road 3-10); northwest on Hogback Road to U.S. Highway 395; northeast on U.S. Highway 395 to U.S. Highway 20; east on U.S. Highway 20 to Burns, point of beginning. The Hart Mountain National Antelope Refuge is closed to all hunting seasons authorized for the Juniper Unit. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: Adopted 10-7-05, ef. 1-1-06 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0072 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Silvies Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Silvies Unit, number 72, is that area beginning at Burns; west on U.S. Highway 20 to Glass Buttes-Camp Creek Road near Glass Buttes; north on Glass Buttes-Camp Creek Road to Twelvemile Creek Road; east on Twelvemile Creek Road to Grindstone Creek Road; northeast on Grindstone Creek Road to Paulina-Suplee Road; southeast on Paulina-Suplee Road to Suplee; east on Pine Creek Road to South Fork John Day River; southeast along South Fork John Day River to Forest Road 3750 at Bear Creek; east on Forest Road 3750 to Forest Road 37; northeast on Forest Road 37 to U.S. Highway 395; south on U.S. Highway 395 to Burns, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0073 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Wagontire Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Wagontire Unit, number 73, is that area beginning 2-1/2 miles east of Millican; southeast on U.S. Highway 20 to U.S. Highway 395; southwest on U.S. Highway 395 to State Highway 31 at Valley Falls; northwest on State Highway 31 to Wagontire Road 9 miles east of Silver Lake; northeast on Wagontire Road to Christmas Valley; east 2 miles on Christmas Valley-Wagontire Road (Lake County Road 5-14) to Lake County Road 5-14C 2 miles east of Christmas Valley; north and north east on Lake County Road 5-14C to junction with Lake County Road 5-14D; continue north on Lake County Road 5-14C to intersection of Lake County Road 5-12B; west on Lake County Road 5-12B to junction of Lake County Road 5-12D; north on Lake County Road 5-12D past Janes Well and Dickerson Well to U.S. Highway 20, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 30-2000, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-14-00 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0074 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Warner Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Warner Unit, number 74, is that area beginning at Lakeview; north east on U.S. Highway 395 to Fort Bidwell-Warner Valley Road north of Abert Lake; south on Fort Bidwell-Warner Valley Road through Plush and Adel to Oregon-California state line; west along state line to U.S. Highway 395 at New Pine Creek; north on U.S. Highway 395 to Lakeview, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0075 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Interstate Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Interstate Unit, number 75, is that area beginning at Bly; west on State Highway 140 to Beatty; north on Godowa Springs Road to Sprague River; west along Sprague River one mile to Sycan River; upstream north and east along Sycan River to Pike's Crossing; east on Forest Road 30 to Forest Road 28; east on Forest Road 28 to Forest Road 29; east on Forest Road 29 to State Highway 31; southeast on State Highway 31 to Valley Falls; south on U.S. Highway 395 to Oregon-California state line; west along state line to Lost River; northwest along Lost River to East Langell Valley Road; north on East Langell Valley Road to Gerber Road; northeast on Gerber Road past Gerber Reservoir to Bly, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0076 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Silver Lake Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Silver Lake Unit, number 76, is that area beginning at Silver Lake; southeast on State Highway 31 to Forest Road 29, 18 miles south of Summer Lake; west on Forest Road 29 to Forest Road 28; west on Forest Road 28 to Forest Road 30; west on Forest Road 30 to Pike's Crossing; downstream north and southwest along Sycan River to Powers Crossing (Teddy Powers Meadow); northwest on road 44 to Yamsey Guard Station at head of Williamson River; north and west along Williamson River to Silver Lake Road; east on Silver Lake Road through Bear Flat to State Highway 31; east on State Highway 31 to Silver Lake, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999, f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 6-16-99 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;635-080-0077 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Fort Rock Unit &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Fort Rock Unit, number 77, is that area beginning at Silver Lake; west on State Highway 31 to Klamath Marsh Road; west on Klamath Marsh Road to Williamson River; west and south along Williamson River returning to Klamath Marsh-Silver Lake Road; west on Klamath Marsh Road to U.S. Highway 97; west on Scott Creek Road 66 one mile to Sand Creek; southwest along Sand Creek to Crater Lake National Park boundary; north and west along Crater Lake National Park boundary to Pacific Crest Trail; north along Pacific Crest Trail to State Highway 58; southeast on State Highway 58 to Crescent Creek; north along Crescent Creek to county road 61 to Crescent; east on county road 61 to Crescent; north on U.S. Highway 97 to Gilchrist main logging road one mile north of Gilchrist; east on Gilchrist main logging road 9775 to State Highway 31 between mileposts 16 and 17; southeast on State Highway 31 to the Fort Rock Road at Horse Ranch; east and south on Fort Rock Road past Fort Rock to Christmas Valley; southwest on Wagontire Road to State Highway 31 nine miles east of Silver Lake; west on State Highway 31 to Silver Lake, point of beginning. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stat. Auth.: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Stats. Implemented: ORS 496.012, ORS 496.138, ORS 496.146 &amp;amp; ORS 496.162 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Hist.: DFW 47-1999,.f. &amp;amp; cert. ef. 1-01-08 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Amended October 2010 &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 0 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs><idCredit>ODFW. 2016. Oregon Administrative Rule - OAR 635-080-0000,
https://www.dfw.state.or.us/OARs/80.pdf</idCredit><searchKeys><keyword>Oregon</keyword><keyword>big game wildlife managemment</keyword><keyword>game bird wildlife management</keyword><keyword>WMU</keyword></searchKeys></dataIdInfo><mdLang><languageCode value="eng" Sync="TRUE"/><countryCode value="USA" Sync="TRUE"/></mdLang><mdChar><CharSetCd value="004" Sync="TRUE"/></mdChar><distInfo><distFormat><formatName Sync="TRUE">Shapefile</formatName></distFormat><distTranOps><transSize Sync="TRUE">8.203</transSize></distTranOps></distInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005" Sync="TRUE"/></mdHrLv><mdHrLvName Sync="TRUE">dataset</mdHrLvName><refSysInfo><RefSystem><refSysID><identCode code="2992" Sync="TRUE"/><idCodeSpace Sync="TRUE">EPSG</idCodeSpace><idVersion Sync="TRUE">8.9.3(9.0.0)</idVersion></refSysID></RefSystem></refSysInfo><spatRepInfo><VectSpatRep><geometObjs Name="ODFW_wildlife_mgmt_units"><geoObjTyp><GeoObjTypCd value="002" Sync="TRUE"></GeoObjTypCd></geoObjTyp><geoObjCnt Sync="TRUE">69</geoObjCnt></geometObjs><topLvl><TopoLevCd value="001" Sync="TRUE"></TopoLevCd></topLvl></VectSpatRep></spatRepInfo><spdoinfo><ptvctinf><esriterm Name="ODFW_wildlife_mgmt_units"><efeatyp Sync="TRUE">Simple</efeatyp><efeageom code="4" Sync="TRUE"></efeageom><esritopo Sync="TRUE">FALSE</esritopo><efeacnt Sync="TRUE">69</efeacnt><spindex Sync="TRUE">TRUE</spindex><linrefer Sync="TRUE">FALSE</linrefer></esriterm></ptvctinf></spdoinfo><eainfo><detailed Name="ODFW_wildlife_mgmt_units"><enttyp><enttypl Sync="TRUE">ODFW_wildlife_mgmt_units</enttypl><enttypt Sync="TRUE">Feature Class</enttypt><enttypc Sync="TRUE">69</enttypc></enttyp><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">FID</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">FID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">OID</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">4</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale><attrdef Sync="TRUE">Internal feature number.</attrdef><attrdefs Sync="TRUE">Esri</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="TRUE">Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Shape</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Shape</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Geometry</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">0</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale><attrdef Sync="TRUE">Feature geometry.</attrdef><attrdefs Sync="TRUE">Esri</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="TRUE">Coordinates defining the features.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">UNIT_NUM</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">UNIT_NUM</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Integer</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">10</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">UNIT_NAME</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">UNIT_NAME</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">30</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Shape_Leng</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Shape_Leng</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Shape_Area</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Shape_Area</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale><attrdef Sync="TRUE">Area of feature in internal units squared.</attrdef><attrdefs Sync="TRUE">Esri</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="TRUE">Positive real numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr></detailed></eainfo><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20190409</mdDateSt></metadata>
